<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Policies on Scratch Addons</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/docs/policies/</link><description>Recent content in Policies on Scratch Addons</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://scratchaddons.com/docs/policies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Security Policy</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/docs/policies/security/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/docs/policies/security/</guid><description>Supported Versions Scratch Addons should not have any security issues in its most recent version, found in the Chrome Web Store and Addons for Firefox.
We only officially support the most recent stable versions of Chrome and Firefox. However, if you found a vulnerability that only occurs if using an old browser version, please report it (see below).
Reporting a Vulnerability If you find a vulnerability within Scratch Addons (any repository belonging to the organization) please contact World_Languages privately by emailing worldxlanguages (at) gmail.</description></item><item><title>Chrome Web Store Privacy Information</title><link>https://scratchaddons.com/docs/policies/chrome-web-store-privacy-information/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://scratchaddons.com/docs/policies/chrome-web-store-privacy-information/</guid><description>This is how we fill the &amp;ldquo;privacy practices&amp;rdquo; form on the Chrome Web Store Developer Dashboard.
Single purpose Allows users to customize their experience on the Scratch website (scratch.mit.edu) by providing previously unavailable features - including many related to reading and replying of Scratch messages/notifications. This extension makes use of the &amp;ldquo;Scratch API&amp;rdquo; (api.scratch.mit.edu).
Permission justification Permission Justification Host permission Used to access information from, and run content scripts on the Scratch website.</description></item></channel></rss>